What is that smell? Is something burning?
Nothing is burning, Mama. It is fresh fish pepper soup. Just how you like it.
Too much water. You want to drown my son? Is this soup or a swimming pool?
Mama, it's actually okay.
You eat poison and call it sugar because of this woman.
Amara, take this rubbish day. Fried plantain for my son.
Mama, Chidi specifically asked for pepper soup. I spent three hours.
And I said take it away. Or are you deaf as well as useless?
Yes. Your mother's blood pressure is more important than your wife's dignity.
Amara, what are you doing? We need to talk about this.
Babe, why are you crying? You know how she is. She's old.
She's old?
I can't. She's not the laundry I did yesterday. She took my sense line.
She wanted it in six months. I talked to her.
But to her privately? I can't show you my mother. She raised me alone.
She raised you to be a husband to her, not to me.
There are three people in this marriage, Chidi, and I am the third wheel.
Please, lower your voice if she hears you.
I am looking for my gold earrings. I know you took them.
I have never touched your jewelry.
Thief! You are a thief!
Chidi, come out! Your wife has stolen my gold.
Mama, what is happening?
Stomach and vagabond. The watchtower has a witness.
Send her away to me. Send her away. Give me another minute.
Chidi, look at me.
Amara, if you took it, just give it back. We can settle this.
You think I stole it?
Okay, I am leaving.
Good riddance.
Good riddance. Go back to your father's hut.
Amara, wait. Don't be dramatic. Where are you going?
Or at least the man who has cut the umbilical cord.
If you walk out that door, Amara, don't come back.
Chidi, look at your mother. She is smiling.
She has won. You are all hers now.
Oh, look, Chidi. I found my tinte. Silly me.
I will make you a goosey soup today, my son.
Better than that rubbish she makes.
You had them the whole time?
And you broke her.
Do you want beef or goat meat, my son?